You don't have to like me, okay?
Huh?
I was satisfied enough confessing to you.
I won't ask for anything more.
- But...
- Besides,
you're lovable to me
like a local mascot would be.
Nothing more than that.
What the heck?
I was serious.
It was all a big misunderstanding?
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Now I've fallen for you for real.
Summer vacation offers many temptations.
But I want you all to be
model students of Kitahara.
Remember, don't do anything crazy, okay?
Yes, ma'am.
Now go enjoy your break!
Hell yeah!
Bye, teach!
Let's go, let's go. Come on, baby.
Yeah, yeah, summer vacay!
- Mayama.
- Huh?
Someone's not excited.
Come on, it's summer break!
Go, go, summer vacay!
Tsunekawada and I were saying
we should all take a trip together.
My vote's in for the beach.
Not an ocean guy?
Then how about a mountain?
Or the opposite, a hot spring?
How's that the opposite?
Sorry.
I'll be busy over break, with my...
my part-time job.
So, yeah.
Hey!
What's his deal?
Guess it'll just be us three.
Then how about the opposite
of hot springs, camping?
You're losing me with these opposites, dude.
At first, I lied about the part-time job.
But I realized it was actually a great idea.
I figured doing busy work
was a good way to forget Asamiya.
Except...
This is no job to do in the summer.
Okay, keep going.
Finally, I'm almost done...
No flyers allowed.
Sorry...
Sakaki?
Impressive vocal range, right?
What are you doing here?
I live here.
Oh, makes sense.
Sorry to bother.
Where are you going?
You said no flyers.
I was joking.
Leave all the flyers you want.
Here, I'll help.
Huh?
How do I do this?
I've never left flyers before.
Uh...
Thanks, I appreciated the help.
Anytime.
Didn't think you were
actually working though.
I thought that was just
an excuse to avoid us.
Uh, well...
Something on your mind?
Huh?
You've been down since the festival, right?
Even I could tell.
If you'd rather not talk,
don't worry about it.
You've had a couple of girlfriends, right?
Yeah, unlike you.
Hey.
I was just wondering
what it meant to like someone.
Thinking of becoming a poet?
I'm being serious here.
When I like someone, I want to be with them.
I'd like to get touchy with them, too.
But aren't there other types of "likes"?
The non-romantic kind.
Oh, the platonic sort of like?
Yeah.
Okay, I understand your conundrum now.
I think your lack of romantic experience
is to blame, though.
Can't deny that.
You need to live a little, Mayama.
It works out, since I'm single, too.
Why is your relationship status
relevant to our conversation?
It's super relevant.
They have room for one more.
You're done with work for the day, right?
- Yeah.
- Then let's go.
Huh?
Hey, wait!
Where are we going?
- Karaoke.
- Huh?
But this is no ordinary karaoke outing.
- Sakaki.
- 'Sup man!
- So...
- We're joining a mixer.
What? I didn't sign up for this.
You wanted to know a girl's heart.
I never said that!
- Just trust me.
- But...
Huh? Sakaki and Mayama.
Asamiya...
- What're you two up to?
- Shopping. You two?
- Can't you tell?
- Hey!
- We're getting ready for a mixer.
- You and your mixers, Sakaki.
- Is Mayama joining you?
- No, I...
Yeah. He begged me to join.
Let's leave them.
- Sure.
- See you two.
Go on.
Head on in.
What're you doing? Come on.
♪ La La Love You A to Z,
I'll never know it's not mutual ♪
♪ La La Love you A to Z ♪
Thank you very much!
Let's get hyped up!
- Yeah!
- Great opener!
You're a good singer.
Here, sing a song and introduce yourself.
Huh? Oh, uh...
Here.
I'm Mayama.
That's all. I'll sing later.
Yeah, give it up!
All right, who's next?
Asamiya definitely misunderstood.
I'll sort through all this...
Your iced coffees. Enjoy.
That was a real shocker, huh?
I didn't think Mayama went to mixers.
Sorry to call on you like this.
You definitely surprised me.
I never thought you'd come to me for advice.
So, what's up?
I have a crush on someone.
Yeah.
You're not surprised?
No, I am.
I've never heard you mention a crush.
So, what are they like?
They're kind.
They prioritize others over themself.
Before I knew it, I liked them.
And I told them how I felt, too.
But...
The other party turned you down?
No. I told them they didn't need to like me.
Why?
Because they're so kind.
Because they're too kind.
I can tell he's desperate
to live up to everyone's expectations.
I didn't want them
to feel forced to like me.
I was worried they would be considerate,
and try to like me out of pity.
And that won't do for you.
Yeah. What I want isn't something like that.
- Woah.
- You play guitar?
I'd be happy if they earnestly fell for me.
But if that weren't the case...
It wouldn't be...
what I wanted from them.
So...
Your romance is a difficult one, huh?
What?
Nothing. I'm just surprised to see
a guy like you worry, too.
I'm not joking around.
Sorry.
If anything, I'm embarrassed.
I've never opened up like this before.
Well, I'm happy to see you fumbling about.
Huh?
Why don't you open up to them like this?
Tell them you're feeling confused,
and tangled up inside.
I'm sure they'll understand.
Or do you not trust
the person you're crushing on?
No, I do.
I'd love to meet them one day.
Since you're so obsessed with them and all.
Mayama?
I'll be rooting for you.
♪ All night, all night, all night, you ♪
You're good!
A natural!
Great job!
Why did I pick a song in English?
I'm going to the restroom.
Your pronunciation was good!
The restroom...
I thought you were a native!
You're making fun of me.
[Karaoke Entertainment BIG ECHO]
- You know, Sakaki's friend we saw earlier.
- Yeah?
Asamiya, I think. He was so good-looking.
He was so high caliber, I'm falling for him.
You have a boyfriend!
I like him for a different reason.
Why are you at this mixer anyway?
Right. Of course Asamiya
wouldn't really like me.
It's just not possible.
I didn't tell him I'd be here.
Then are you aiming for someone?
Hey.
What are you doing?
I came looking for you.
For me?
And now that I've found you,
I've decided to watch you freeze in place.
Wait.
Go home.
You're the one who drew the line first.
Encore, encore!
Welcome back.
Here.
Sing us a song.
- He's singing?
- Finally!
What're you gonna sing?
- An English song?
- Seriously, stop that!
Asamiya?
The good-looking guy from earlier!
We're leaving.
Where are they going?
Home, I guess.
Did you enjoy the mixer?
I was dragged into it.
I'm jealous of Sakaki.
He gets to be all touchy with you.
Huh?
Did you do this sort of thing with him?
Of course not.
And this?
How does this make you feel?
I don't know.
It's all a first for me.
Your face is red.
I haven't been able to see you
since summer vacation began.
It's been bothering me a lot.
I wanted you to be around more.
You're playing dirty.
How are you expecting me to respond?
I don't get you, Asamiya.
You're the one who drew the line.
Don't jump over it again.
Sorry.
I...
I was seriously thinking about you.
I know you'd never get it,
since you're so perfect, but...
I'm not perfect.
Huh?
You overheard those girls, right?
All my life,
I've been judged for my looks.
Everyone expects the best from me.
When I fail, they say I'm just a face.
They're all quick to be disappointed.
I'm constantly struggling to stay afloat.
Honestly, I'm a wreck right now.
My feelings are already out of whack
because you're sitting next to me.
I don't want to hurt you.
I want to clear up the misunderstanding.
It's all a tangled mess in my head.
But...
I want to seem composed in front of you.
I want to look calm and cool.
What misunderstanding?
You're not a mascot.
I didn't want you to "like" me out of pity,
and not actually feel that way.
That's why I made that excuse.
What?
But...
I went about it the wrong way.
I'm sorry.
Then...
Whenever you said you liked me...
You didn't mean it platonically?
I obviously meant it romantically.
I want to hold hands with you.
I want to hug you tight.
And...
I want to be with you whenever I can.
Mayama?
What a relief.
I thought I had no chance.
Sorry.
Liking you, "out of pity"?
I wouldn't do that.
So, don't draw a line between us anymore.
I won't.
Asamiya.
I like you, okay?
In what way?
Huh?
I told you exactly what I meant.
So, tell me.
What do you mean when you "like" me?
I want to touch you.
I also want to hold hands with you.
I want to hug you tight, too.
That's what my "like" means.
Sorry.
It's fine.
I liked that.
Your phone's buzzing.
See you soon...
Kou.
I'm the boyfriend.
I know.
Want to go together?
Let's make real summer memories.
I didn't think it'd be a gig at the festival.
Kou!
Who is she to Asamiya?